https://www.clearstands.com/privacy-statement/

Created with Sketch.
Created with Sketch.
Privacy Statement
Piasa Plastics, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm's commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the following website: www.clearstands.com. Piasa Plastics, Inc. has adopted a set of guidelines which serve as the basis for our relationship with customers via our website. These guidelines have been developed with the understanding that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, these guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page.
Collection and Use of Information
In general, you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. In order to better provide you with services, our site collects two types of information about its visitors: Non-Personally Identifiable Information and Personally Identifiable Information.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
You should be aware that the computer that hosts our website collects a record of your visit to our site and logs the following information for statistical purposes:
the full Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the Web page from which you came to our website
your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, which may include a domain name
the date and time for each page you view
the name of and information about any website or advertisement that brought you to our website
searches you perform (if applicable)
links you click on
computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform
Our site employs the use of cookies so we can track the pages of our website that you view and the order in which you view them. A cookie is a small data file consisting of numbers, letters, or other characters that our server sends to your browser and stores on your computer's hard drive when you visit our website. The web server can access this cookie when you return to the website. The cookie automatically identifies your computer, but not your identity, to our servers while you use our website.
Piasa Plastics, Inc. may share the Non-Personally Identifiable Information it tracks, in aggregate form, with certain service providers in order to improve the quality and type of information presented on our website.
No attempt will be made to identify users except, in the unlikely event of an investigation, where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect our service provider's logs.
Personally Identifiable Information
Our web site also allows you the opportunity to voluntarily provide us with Personally Identifiable Information in order to better provide you with services. This information lets us know the specifics of who you are and can be used to identify, contact or locate you. Personally Identifiable Information may consist of: your name, address, telephone number, email address, and any other information you may provide us via one of our website's intake forms.
Piasa Plastics, Inc. will use the information you provide us in order to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, except in the unlikely event of an investigation where a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect our communication records. We also do not sell, rent or share email addresses with any third party, advertiser or other partners.
Your Access and Control Over Information
If you have provided us with Personally Identifiable Information, you may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website. You may also contact us to request that we make corrections, changes, additions, or deletions to any of the Personally Identifiable Information we have on file about you.
Links
This web site may, from time-to-time, contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects Personally Identifiable Information.
×
OK
